

SALAH MORGAN

Retail & Management

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Address

DUBAI

Contact

+971558118159 salah.m.morgan@gmail.com

Date of Birth 21.05.1987

LANGUAGES

English



Arabic



SOFTWARE SKILLS

Word



Microsoft Excel



PROFILE

Enthusiastic and energetic individual with 5 years of retail and customer service experience in Dubai seeking a position to gain and share unique experience with many new challenges and competitions. A team player who is always willing to improve and reach the highest goals.

EDUCATION

09.2004 - 06.2010

Helwan University, Tourism and hotels management faculty ,Egypt
Bachelor degree (quidance department)

SKILLS

- ✓ Good communication written and oral skills
- ✓ Execute assigned tasks and responsibilities to customary or specified standards within a certain time-frame.
- ✓ Work under pressure

EXPERIENCE

04.2017 - present

Al Futtaim Watches and Jewellery

Retail Sales Representative

- Opening and closing procedure following with emails, reports, receiving deliveries, transferring orders, requisitions, inventory.
- Providing exceptional customer service by greeting, assisting and demonstrating an excellent knowledge of the product.
- Ensuring the achievement of individual and store targets and goals.
- Always keeping up with fashion trends and developments in luxury market.
- Managing the visual display of the products in accordance with company standards and brands image.

05.2014 - 02.2017

Jashanmal LLC

Senior Sales Executive

- Offer explanation on latest fashion trends, products information including quality and after sale assistance.
- Engage on conversation to understand customers needing and offer products which suit and exceed their expectations.
- Counter check the selling price and unit cost of each items of stock.
- Have a good customer relations and sales performance. Product knowledge and maintains selling techniques
- Answering questions and resolving problems and service issues.

PERSONALITY

- ✓ Communicative
- **✓** Punctuality
- ✓ Creativity
- ✓ Organized

DRIVING LICENSE

Available

02.2013 - 01.2014

Etisalat (UAE)

Customer Service Agent

- Handle customer's issues and complains and solve any problems using the technical support or information's
- Explain new offers and promotions to customers and activate new services
- Open customer accounts by recording account information

11.2010 - 12.2012

Cairo Express Travel

Tour Leader

- Assisting tourists with their arrival and departure at the airport
- Provide excellent help and assistance with the client throughout the duration of their stay.
- Act as a day to day guide and manages the group of clients
- Provide support during emergencies or situations during their stay in the city
- Develop, recommend and promote the business by organizing group activities to guests